hello brothers and sisters this is ey on
ey censored Supernatural Bible changes
on YouTube and today is the 9th of
January 2024 and I want to go ahead and
introduce and do a book review on this
book that I I wrote and it's just been
published uh this month or maybe it was
at the end of last month but anyway I
titled it Islamic language invades the
Bible Supernatural Bible
changes and
our bibles are under satanic assault and
supernaturally changing and it's going
to be used as a weapon against True
Believers that that really is the
truth we are seeing our Bible is being
invaded by Foreign word Invaders
Doctrine grammar errors punctuation
errors and it's supernatural the Bible's
next to our beds on our bedside tables
in our bookshelves on our coffee tables
wherever it is in your
house they're changing supernaturally
and it's absolutely
bizarre but it's
undeniable and it's very clear that
second Thessalonians 2 is coming to pass
now I've been covering these satanic
change of scripture for 7 and A2 years
on YouTube I
spent so much time every day I have to
say for the past 7 and a half
years either thinking about this
researching it praying through it crying
about
it because I am wholly grieved that our
bibles are supernaturally changing but I
cannot deny it and I hope you don't
either the Bible is is changing and the
Antichrist is rising in
scripture and we see different agendas
at play here and one of the agendas is
the Islamic invasion in our own Bibles
now I'm going to go ahead and give you a
sneak peek I'm going to show you a
little bit of my manuscript here the
table of contents and I cover the truth
that's found in Jesus Christ salvation
only found in Jesus Christ very
important for me to declare that in the
beginning I go in I talk about Abraham
Isaac and ishmail that's right because I
will tell you now that ishma is taking
prominence now in our
Bibles Ishmael was like an afterthought
if you will he was if you remember an
illegitimate son of
Abraham because Abraham had relations
with Hagar the concubine and gave birth
to an
ishmail but now the Bible says that
Abraham married Hagar making ishmail
legitimate and also we see that ishma
now
has 12 sons that he calls princes they
all have castles and they're called
dukes and on and on it
goes there are now five I think five or
six I think there's six different
ishs in the
[Music]
Bible so I'll just leave it there but
that's a huge start with the changes in
scripture related to
Islam because we know that is ishmail
was the birth of the Arab
Nations I give an overview of Islam I
talk about the Holy Land Wars because of
course we're seeing that happen today
between Gaza and Israel and one thing I
realized is that in this book I do not
include
Gaza but now that I think about it I
might just do an addition uh a revision
on this because I forgot to include that
because Gaza is in the Bible now but
anyway I talk about the Abraham Accords
and if you're not familiar with that you
need to do your
research but there was a peace treaty
signed between some Islamic countries
and the United States in 2020 I
believe and it is
relevant and then I go in I talk about
the Bible changes and I segment them
out brothers and
sisters what we are seeing happen is a
changing of scripture to prepare the way
for the
Antichrist the Antichrist will pretend
that he's God and he he will deceive
many and there will be a great falling
away cuz they will worship
Him and the
Bible is changing and placing a
counterfeit
Jesus in
scripture we have new doctrine in the
Bible and I will tell you another
Islamic change it's
huge in Luke
19:27 I believe that's correct
now says it's a
parable and Jesus was giving a parable
and commands them to go ahead and slay
their
enemies and I'm paraphrasing go look at
it in your own Bible it's change a
universal change Spanish Bible is to
decapitate and by the way there's a lot
more beheadings in the Bible today I
cover that as
well I this book is really important
because we see an Islamic Invasion not
just in our
Bibles but here in Western
Nations currently with the open
borders and the allowance
[Music]
for is Islam Sharia law to be exercised
in Western
nations of course we need to pray that
Mim would have an encounter with the
Living God and be set free in jesus'
name and praise the Lord many Muslims
across the world are having dreams and
visions and being set free by the king
of kings and Lord of lords this
particular religion it's an ideology
that's really
wicked
absolutely and our nations are being
invaded here here is the book on Amazon
you can buy it on paperback
$12 and it's in Kindle version for less
than $10 you can download it today and
um there it is on Amazon you can also
check it out I have it here on my
website too B- ches.com and I have a
list of all my books here but that being
said brothers and
sisters the Islamic language that's
invading scripture is
undeniable and we are
seeing doctrinal
changes that are Islamic stories in
Scripture that are
changing to blend Christianity and Islam
to chrislam we've all heard about
that so brothers and sisters what's most
important is you pray and fast and seek
the Lord ask the Holy Spirit to give you
wisdom and discernment I don't have all
the
answers seek the Lord ask him to show
you what the truth
is it's most important eternity is at
stake and I've been studying this for 7
and 1/2 years and I see the changes are
only
accelerating be strong and courageous
brothers and sisters do not fear or be
dismayed for the Lord your God is with
you wherever you go until next time